

iOS Developer

Michał Krupa



Get in contact

+48 512-294-004 michal.krupa.dev@gmail.com Kawiory 39/12, 30-055 Kraków



I am a passionate mobile application programmer. I used to created websites in high school, also I am hobbyist videographer. I have worked in teams of several people and as single programmer. New experiences are very valuable to me, that's why I like to write any kind of applications for various of purposes.

Professional experience

Programming languages

★★★ Swift

★★☆ Objective-C, C, C++, Java

★☆☆ PHP, JavaScript

ios sdk

UlKit, Foundation, GCD, CoreData, CoreBluetooth, CoreLocation, CoreMotion, UserNotifications, SpriteKit, SceneKit, ARKit, AVFoundation and others...

Tools/Frameworks

Apple Developer Program, Git, RestAPI, JSON, SourceTree, Charles, Firebase, TeamCity, CocoaPods, Moya, Alamofire, Shell, PromiseKit, JIRA, Confluence

Design patters

MVC, MVVM, VIPER, Fabryka, Fasada, Prototyp, Koordynator, Obserwator, Singletone

Other skills

Knowledge of Adobe Premiere, After Effects, Photoshop; driving licence, English language B2



Employment history

Comarch S.A. Oct. 2019 - May 2020

- Working on banking app GoMobile Biznes,
- Writing tests of different kind: shakedown, UI and Unit,
- Bug-fixing, code refactor

Mediaflex sp.z o o Oct. 2016 - Sep. 2019

- Creating app from medical field and supporting sales representatives of Polpharma S.A.,
- Administrating account of Apple Developer Program,
- Participating in process of setting requirements and designing mobile apps

Netigen sp.j. Apr. 2016 - Sep. 2016

• Writing simple mobile applications

Adluna May 2015 - Oct. 2015

• Developing application for museums which main functionality was based on connection with Buetooth beacons



Featured projects

ReColGnizer - application for color defining and recognising in different colorspaces. It is a private project but some of the code is available to check on my GitHub

Kardiometr - application for Mediaflex company. I have participated in refactoring it and adding new features. It is directed for hypertensive patients and main functionality is based on saving measurements in CoreData, downloaded via Bluetooth from preasure gauge. It also sends notifications with different kinds of reminders, prints charts, alerts main doctor and many other. It is available on **AppStore**



Education hisotory

Studies at the AGH University of Science and Technology

Sep. 2010 - Mar. 2016

• Field of applied computer science in faculty of metal engineering and industrial computer science

Education in High school nr. 1 in Tarnów

Sep. 2007 - May 2010

A class with a mathematics and computer science profile

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)